188games.com 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy at 188BET – Corporate Affairs - 188BET

Your privacy on the Internet is very important to 188BET and its owner and operator, Cube Limited. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us in order to allow you to enjoy playing online at 188BET. 

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you:

  * Introduction
  * What information is collected and for what purpose?
  * Visitor Information
  * Confidentiality
  * Use and Storage of your personal information
  * Keeping your data secure
  * Limits of confidentiality
  * Who receives your information?
  * Monitoring
  * Access to your personal information and your rights
  * Marketing and opting out
  * Cookies
  * Consent to Privacy Policy
  * Who are we?

INTRODUCTION

This website is brought to you by Cube Limited. We take the privacy of our website users very seriously. We want our services to be safe and enjoyable environments for our audience. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy (“the Policy”) carefully as it contains certain information about how we will use your personal data.

In order to provide you with the full range of services, we are sometimes required to collect information about you. The Policy covers the use of personal information that is collected when you use 188BET. The Policy also gives you information about cookies.

From time to time you maybe asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name, postal address, email address, membership number, telephone or mobile number, date of birth or payment details) in order to use the Services and the Site. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this Policy. When using your personal information we will act in accordance with current legislation and will aim to meet current best practice.

We may also monitor your use of this website. This may include monitoring how many times you visit, which pages you go to, and the originating domain name of a user's internet service provided. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually.

WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND FOR WHAT PURPOSE

As part of the 188BET Account Opening process, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including a name, postal address, e-mail address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for use of the 188BET services is greater than 18. We may use your personal information to confirm various financial transactions, to occasionally send you events and news information to provide you with customer support services and to provide a full and effective gaming service. If in time newsletters are sent and you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter. The name you register with must be yours. In addition, it is very important that you complete the account details with valid information, since they will be used in the course of validating financial transactions and the other aforementioned purposes.

Players are able to change account details by selecting an Account option in the downloaded software.

VISITOR INFORMATION

During the course of any visit to the Site the pages you see, along with a short text file called a “cookie” are downloaded to your computer. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the computer (and probably it user) has visited the website before.

188BET uses cookies and collects IP addresses. Information supplied by cookies and IP addresses can help us to provide you with a better online user experience and assist us to analyse the profile of our visitors. This information is not used to develop a personal profile of you and the log files are regularly purged.

CONFIDENTIALITY

188BET undertakes substantial efforts to protect your confidentiality, identity, preferences and other information it has collected about you and we will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside 188BET, other than as described in this Policy.

All 188BET employees are required to comply with the terms of this Policy. This Policy provides that employees are obligated to keep your information strictly confidential. This obligation continues once an employee has left 188BET.

You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your 188BET Player password is confidential and we recommend that you not divulge it to anyone or enable others to discover it.

USE AND STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you supply any personal information to 188BET we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use that data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular web pages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.

The purposes for which we may use your data include:

  * to help us identify you and any accounts you hold with us
  * service administration purposes
  * statistical analysis
  * marketing – see "Marketing and opting out" below
  * fraud prevention and detection
  * to notify you of any changes to this website or our service which may affect you
  * security vetting
  * improving our services..

You will be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use as detailed below.

We may contact you:

  * in relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the services to you
  * where you have opted to receive further correspondence
  * to invite you to participate in surveys about our services (participation is always voluntary)
  * for marketing purposes where you have specifically agreed to this (see below)

We will keep your information confidential except where disclosure is required or permitted by law (for example to government bodies and law enforcement agencies or as described below where there is offensive or inappropriate content on the website) or as described below in relation to our business partners. Generally we will only use your information within 188BET; however sometimes we may use third parties to process your information (e.g. providers of web hosting, maintenance services, security, credit agencies). We may also use third parties to carry out checks on devices you use in accessing our Services for risk vetting and your own protection. Vetting may involve placing a cookie or other file on your device to collect and process technical data on your device. To the extent that such third parties are data processors, we will require those third parties to comply strictly with our instructions and we will require that they do not use your personal information for their own business purposes.

We may also share your personal data with our business partners for marketing purposes as detailed below.

Where we reasonably believe that you are or may be in breach of any of the laws of the Isle of Man we may use your personal information to inform relevant third parties such as your employer, educational establishment or law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour.

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of 188BET membership you no longer wish to continue your registration as a 188BET member, subject to Data Protection legislation and regulatory requirements. For safety reasons, however, we may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of 188BET for a period of 12 months. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other 188BET services (e.g. competitions), that information will be held as long as is necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly.

We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 2002 (an Act of Tynwald).

KEEPING YOUR DATA SECURE

We will use technical and organizational measures to safeguard your personal data, for example:

  * access to your account is controlled by password and username which are unique to you
  * we store your personal data on secure servers

Whilst we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data which are transferred from you or to you via the internet.

LIMITS OF CONFIDENTIALITY

Due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, 188BET may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information about our Players. 188BET will use its best reasonable efforts to limit such disclosure to the following:

  * where 188BET believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena, warrant or other legal process; or
  * where reasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce 188BET' rights.

Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your identification, name, street address, city, post code, country, phone number, e-mail, and company to third party agents of 188BET as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity or activity that may expose us to legal liability.

WHO RECEIVES YOUR INFORMATION?

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained above, we may disclose your personal information to our employees, employees of other companies related to or affiliated with 188BET and to third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us in respect of your being a user of 188BET (including, but not limited to, security, credit and risk vetting agencies). The third party service providers may check any details we disclose against any databases (public or private) to which they have access and will keep a record of that check.

We may also obtain personal information about you from third party service providers. You agree that we may process, use, record and disclose personal information which you provide to us, or that we receive from third party service providers and that such personal data may be recorded by us or them. We reserve the right, based on the information we receive from you or obtain from third party service providers, to suspend or close your 188BET membership account at any time.

MONITORING

We may monitor and record communications with you (such as telephone conversation and email) for the purpose of quality assurance, fraud prevention and compliance.

ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. The current fee for information requests is £10.

Please address requests to the Data Protection Officer, Cube Limited, Ground Floor, St George’s Court, Upper Church Street, Douglas, Isle of Man, IM1 1EE. You should:

  * put your request in writing
  * include proof of your identity and address (e.g. a certified copy of your driving licence or passport and a recent utility or credit card bill)
  * attach a cheque in the sum of £10 made payable to Cube Limited
  * specify the personal data you want access to, including any account or reference numbers where applicable.

You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. If you wish to exercise this right you should:

  * put your request in writing
  * provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, username, registration details)
  * specify the information that is incorrect and what it should be replaced with.

You also have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If you wish to exercise this right you should:

  * put your request in writing (an email simply with a header that says “unsubscribe” is acceptable
  * provide us with enough information to identify you (e.g. account number, username, registration details)

If your objection is not to direct marketing in general, but to direct marketing by a particular channel (e.g. email or telephone) please specify the channel you are objecting to.

MARKETING AND OPTING OUT

We may share your personal data with organisations who are our business partners and we or they may contact you, unless you have asked us or them not to do so, by mail, telephone, SMS text, fax, email or other available means of communication about products, services, promotions or special offers.

If you prefer not to receive any further marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. See further “Access to your personal information and your rights” above.

Un-subscription from receiving any marketing material may take up to two (2) business days to take effect

COOKIES

We may send you a temporary cookie when you visit www.188BET.com website. A cookie is a text-only string of information that we place in your computer's cookie file so that we can remember who you are when you revisit the Site website. We may use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept the cookie from us and you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser.

CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY

By opening an Account with 188BET, you agree to the terms of this Policy. We may occasionally update this Policy and we therefore encourage you to periodically review it. If we change our Policy we will post the changes on this page. Your continued use of the 188BET services will be deemed acceptance of the updated or amended terms. If you do not agree to the changes you should cease using this website. If there is any conflict between these terms and specific local terms appearing elsewhere on 188BET then the latter shall prevail.

WHO ARE WE?

Cube Limited

Ground Floor

St George's Court

Upper Church Street

Douglas

Isle of Man

IM1 1EE

Last updated on 07 March 2014 12:01 (GMT-4)
